<resources>
    <string name="app_name">solution</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable1">activityFable1</string>
    <string name="Fable_1_text">Long ago, the mice had a general council to consider what measures they could take to outwit their common enemy, the Cat.\n

Some said this, and some said that; but at last a young mouse got up and said he had a proposal to make, which he thought would meet the case.\n

"You will all agree," said he, "that our chief danger consists in the sly and treacherous manner in which the enemy approaches us.\n Now, if we could receive some signal of her approach, we could easily escape from her. \nI venture, therefore, to propose that a small bell be procured, and attached by a ribbon round the neck of the Cat. By this means we should always know when she was about, and could easily retire while she was in the neighbourhood."

This proposal met with general applause, until an old mouse got up and said:\n

"That is all very well, but who is to bell the Cat?"\n

The mice looked at one another and nobody spoke./n Then the old mouse said:\n

"It is easy to propose impossible remedies."\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable2_ctivity">Fable2_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_2_text">A Waggoner was once driving a heavy load along a very muddy way.\n

    At last he came to a part of the road where the wheels sank half-way into the mire,\n and the more the horses pulled, the deeper sank the wheels.\n

    So the Waggoner threw down his whip, and knelt down and prayed to Hercules the Strong.\n

    "O Hercules, help me in this my hour of distress," quoth he.\n

    But Hercules appeared to him, and said:\n

    "Tut, man, don't sprawl there. Get up and put your shoulder to the wheel."\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable3_ctivity">Fable3_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_3_text">An Ass congratulated a Horse on being so ungrudgingly and carefully provided for,\n while he himself had scarcely enough to eat, nor even that without hard work.

    But when war broke out, the heavy armed soldier mounted the Horse, and rushed into the very midst of the enemy,\n and the Horse, being wounded, fell dead on the battle-field.

    Then the Ass, seeing all these things,\n changed his mind, and commiserated the Horse, saying: "How much more fortunate am I than a charger.\n I can remain at home in safety while he is exposed to all the perils of war."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable4_ctivity">Fable4_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_4_text">A Jay venturing into a yard where Peacocks used to walk, found there a number of feathers which had fallen from the Peacocks when they were moulting.

    He tied them all to his tail and strutted down towards the Peacocks.

    When he came near them they soon discovered the cheat, and striding up to him pecked at him and plucked away his borrowed plumes.

    So the Jay could do no better than go back to the other Jays, who had watched his behaviour from a distance; but they were equally annoyed with him, and told him:

    "It is not only fine feathers that make fine birds"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable5_ctivity">Fable5_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_5_text">On a summer day, when the great heat induced a general thirst, a Lion and a Boar came at the same moment to a small well to drink.

    They fiercely disputed which of them should drink first, and were soon engaged in the agonies of a mortal combat.

    On their stopping on a sudden to take breath for the fiercer renewal of the strife, they saw some Vultures waiting in the distance to feast on the one which should fall first.

    They at once made up their quarrel, saying:

    "It is better for us to make friends, than to become the food of Crows or Vultures, as will certainly happen if we are disabled."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable6_ctivity">Fable6_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_6_text">
    A Man and a Lion were discussing the relative strength of men and lions in general.

    The Man contended that he and his fellows were stronger than lions by reason of their greater intelligence.

    "Come now with me," he cried, "and I will soon prove that I am right."

    So he took him into the public gardens and showed him a statue of Hercules overcoming the Lion and tearing his mouth in two.

    "That is all very well," said the Lion, "but proves nothing, for it was a man who made the statue."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable7_ctivity">Fable7_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_7_text">A Lion once fell in love with a beautiful maiden and proposed marriage to her parents.

    The old people did not know what to say.

    They did not like to give their daughter to the Lion, yet they did not wish to enrage the King of Beasts.

    At last the father said:

    "We feel highly honoured by your Majesty's proposal, but you see our daughter is a tender young thing, and we fear that in the vehemence of your affection you might possibly do her some injury. Might I venture to suggest that your Majesty should have your claws removed, and your teeth extracted, then we would gladly consider your proposal again."

    The Lion was so much in love that he had his claws trimmed and his big teeth taken out.

    But when he came again to the parents of the young girl they simply laughed in his face, and bade him do his worst.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable8_ctivity">Fable8_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_8_text">
    A Cock, scratching for food for himself and his hens, found a precious stone; on which he said:

    "If thy owner had found thee, and not I, he would have taken thee up, and have set thee in thy first estate; but I have found thee for no purpose.

    I would rather have one barleycorn than all the jewels in the world."
    </string>


    <string name="title_activity_fable9_ctivity">Fable9_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_9_text">A Hound, who in the days of his youth and strength had never yielded to any beast of the forest, encountered in his old age a boar in the chase.

    He seized him boldly by the ear, but could not retain his hold because of the decay of his teeth, so that the boar escaped.

    His master, quickly coming up, was very much disappointed, and fiercely abused the dog.

    The Hound looked up and said: "It was not my fault, master; my spirit was as good as ever, but I could not help mine infirmities. I rather deserve to be praised for what I have been, than to be blamed for what I am."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable10_ctivity">Fable10_ctivity</string>
    <string name="Fable_10_text">"Be quiet now," said an old Nurse to a child sitting on her lap.

    "If you make that noise again I will throw you to the Wolf."

    Now it chanced that a Wolf was passing close under the window as this was said.

    So he crouched down by the side of the house and waited.

    "I am in good luck to-day," thought he. "It is sure to cry soon, and a daintier morsel I haven't had for many a long day."

    So he waited, and he waited, and he waited, till at last the child began to cry, and the Wolf came forward before the window, and looked up to the Nurse, wagging his tail.

    But all the Nurse did was to shut down the window and call for help, and the dogs of the house came rushing out.

    "Ah," said the Wolf as he galloped away, "Enemies promises were made to be broken."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable1_">Fable1_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable2_">Fable2_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable3_">Fable3_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable4_">Fable4_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable5_">Fable5_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable6_">Fable6_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable7_">Fable7_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable8_">Fable8_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable9_">Fable9_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable10_">Fable10_Activity</string>

</resources>
